http://www.gcfa.org/privacy-policy

×
Welcome to our new site.
We designed this with you in mind.
Easily find forms at the bottom of the homepage, and be sure to check out services that we offer to many organizations.
We also invite your feedback.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last revised in February 2018.
Introduction
This Privacy Policy describes The General Council on Finance and Administration of the United Methodist Church (“GCFA,” “we,” “us” or “our”) use and sharing of (1) personally identifiable information (“PII”) that users (“users” or “you”) voluntarily provide to GCFA when using the website and services delivered through the domain gcfa.org (the “Site”) and (2) certain information about you (described in more detail below) that is automatically collected when you access the Site. By using, accessing, visiting, or registering with the Site, or by submitting your information through it, you consent to this Privacy Policy and to GCFA’s collection and sharing of your PII and other certain information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not use the Site.
We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, effective upon the date we post the new Privacy Policy to the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your binding acceptance of the Privacy Policy, including any changes or modifications that we may make, and to GCFA’s collection and sharing of your PII and other certain information in accordance with the terms of the then current Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use the Site.
Information We Collect
We collect information you share through the Site. We may collect PII you provide, such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or other identifiers.
Our web server collects and stores the following information about you: the date and time of your visit; where you go in our sites; the type of operating system and browser you use; the search engine and key words used that brought you to one of our sites; and the location of a visitor’s machine. This information is collected automatically. We solely use it to improve our websites by tracking the number of “hits” or visits to our sites, the most popular times of day and sections visited, and the range of computers and browsers most commonly used to view it. GCFA does not sell or transmit any of this information to other parties or organizations.
We may use “cookies,” which are small files stored on your computer’s hard drive that are used to store and track information about users. Cookies are used to remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some Site pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.
GCFA may also collect Internet protocol addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to track a user’s session while the user remains anonymous. We analyze this data for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there.
When you send email or other communications to GCFA, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services. We may use your email address to send periodic emails if you decide to opt-in to our mailing list. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may unsubscribe at the bottom of each email.
What Information is Shared and With Whom
We do not rent or sell your PII to outside marketers. GCFA may share your information with its affiliates, subsidiaries or divisions and with their respective officers, directors, employees,accountants, attorneys and agents. In certain circumstances, we may share your information with service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services.
We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials inaccordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. There may be instances when we may access or disclose your information in order to protect or defend the legal rights or property of GCFA and its affiliated companies or their employees and agents, to protect the safety and security of users, and to protect against fraud. We may also access or disclose your information to comply with a court order or other legal process, enforce our Terms of Service, or respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties. GCFA may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets in connection with a merger, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. In such an event, PII may be one of the assets transferred.
Collection of Personal Information from Children
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. This Site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person who we know is a child under the age of 13.
California Rights
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to requestinformation regarding the disclosure of your PII by GCFA to a third party for the third party'sdirect marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using the contact information provided below.
Third Party Websites
This privacy policy is applicable only to GCFA’s website and does not apply to any third partywebsites or to other companies or persons. The Site may contain links to, and media and other content from, other sites. In addition, such third-party media and content may also contain external links. Because of the dynamic media capabilities of the Site, it may not be clear to you which links are embedded in the Site and which are embedded in third-party media and/or content. GCFA cannot and does not guarantee the privacy policies and practices of any third party. GCFA does not control, operate, or endorse any information, products, or services of any third-party websites that may be reached through links from the Site. The use of any personal information provided by you to such a third party will be governed by that party’s privacy policy. If you are unsure whether a web site is controlled, affiliated, or managed by GCFA, you should review the privacy policy at each linked web site to determine how that site treats your personal information.
Security
We take reasonable precautions to protect the security of the PII that you share with us.Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our Site, and you do so at your own risk.
Contact Information
To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and the Company's privacy practices,contact us at GCFA@gcfa.org.
